

Calin Szekely

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- (in) @calin-szekely
- https://calin.codes
- contact@calin.codes
- O Bucharest, Romania

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Developer

NewTech Academy - Romania February 2022 - present

Introduction to Computer Science

HarvardX - Cs50X June 2022 - present

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS3
- WordPress
- SCSS
- Angular
- TypeScript
- NodeJS
- WebPack
- ViteJS
- Firebase
- Git

PROFILE

Determined Web Developer with a passion for creating responsive websites. Experienced in JavaScript, CSS3 and HTML5. I am also dedicated to learning additional coding languages and technologies and currently I am gaining skills in Angular and TypeScript.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer in WordPress -Freelancer Jan 2020 - Present

- Developed and maintained a website in WordPress
- SEO based content writer, work which ranked on google search results with multiple keywords

Web Developer - Freelancer Jan 2022 - present

 Planned, developed, tested, deployed and maintained web applications

INTERESTS

- Blockchain technology
- Web3
- Cryptography
- Motor sports
- And I love to travel